

LUIS DELGADO

NETWORK ENGINEER

Profile

I am a qualified and professional network engineer with six years of experience in provisioning and troubleshooting issues. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for details to solve issues and to keep network running smooth.

EXPERIENCE

NETWORK ENTERPRISE ENGINEER III

KCI/Charter

2023-2024

- Deploying new services on new devices.
- · Configuring, updating, upgrading, and replacing routers and switches.
- Implementing Dinamic Routing Protocols to extend or TS network.

NETWORK ENGINEER

Summit-Broadband

2016-2023

- Provisioning services on a diversity of networks, merging devices brands in a stable network.
- Migrating customers from Legacy networks to a new redundant layer 3 network. Adding new segments on DWDM.

TECH SUPPORT FIELD TECH

Custom Cable Services

2013 - 2014

- Installing services to customer for internet, cable and phone, with coax from tab to demarcation, and from there to each device.
- Fixing service issues, as a contractor for residential customers from Charter.

618-660-4179

ledd264@gmail.com

1336 Stanford Rd, Bethlehem PA

https://j3ccandela.com/

EDUCATION

NEW HORIZON

CCNA, CCNA Security, Network plus

2016-2017

PROFFESIONAL DOCTORATE

Dentistry School in Mexico

1982-1989

SKILLS

- Team Management
- Good Network Troubleshooter
- Fast learner
- Bilingual
- Team player
- Juniper, Ciena, Cisco and Nokia.
- Office, Word, Excel for templates.
- Multitasking.